Contact

9926333000 (Home) rajshamani29@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rajshamani (LinkedIn)

rajshamani.com (Personal) www.youtube.com/watch (Other) jadugar.in (Company)

Top Skills

Entrepreneurship
Public Speaking

Business Strategy

Languages

Spanish

English

Certifications

Digital Marketing

Publications

Raj Shamani: The 'Useless Kid' Influencing The World One Person At A Time

Meet Raj Shamani: That Useless Kid' That's On A Mission To Make People Useful

Top 5 young influencers of India

Raj Shamani

I help organizations & employees build brands & become one, on autopilot mode | Keynote Speaker | Founder @Shamani Industries| Featured: Top 10 Young Entrepreneurs of India |United Nations| Business Influencer

Mumbai Suburban

Summary

- Delivered 200+ Speeches in 26+ Countries on business, branding, GROWTH & mental health
- One of the Youngest Indians to Represent India in UNITED NATIONS
- Started from 0 at the age of 16.
- Built FMCG / CPG brand worth \$20 million through Brand Building,
 Social Media and Growth Hacking strategies.
- Grew a Founder & CEO's Instagram following from 4k to 580k in 7 months.
- Boosted a doctor's patient count by 10x in 1 year.
- Helped a Lawyer-CA expand the client base from 10 clients to 546 across India.

Want to achieve these staggering numbers with ZERO time investment?

Hi, I'm Raj Shamani. And I can help YOU achieve these numbers, just like I've achieved them for myself and my clients over the past few years.

I strongly believe that personal branding and social media is a game changer in today's world. Being online is critical for your business brand, but even more important, is building YOURSELF as a brand.

Yes, I also understand that you have a business to run and a world to change, and do not have much time for your personal brand. So, I'm on a mission to equip YOU with the power of the virtual world and help you find opportunities through social media!

And of course, I practice what I preach.

Over the past few years, I have built myself as the Founder of Shamani Industries. So, when I launched my CPG brand "Insurance" during the pandemic, we hit a revenue of \$1million in just 50 days. During a lockdown. That's the power of a personal brand.

I've also been on the "Top 5 Young Influencers of India" list, and the Youngest Indian to speak at the United Nations Assembly in Vienna. So far, I've given 4 TEDx Talks and over 200 keynotes in 26+ countries. My passion for entrepreneurship and love for speaking has landed me on stages like Jaguar Land Rover, TCS, Reliance, Forbes, Babson College and more.

I love speaking so much, that I recently started a podcast #FiguringOut, one of the Top 10 Business Podcasts of India.

Now that you know a little about me, it's my turn to know a little about you.

Want me to help you grow your digital presence? Want me to help you 10x your client base? Want me to help you multiply your revenue?

Write me at raj@shamani.in or DM me on LinkedIn

Experience

Shamani Industries
Founder
December 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months)
Indore, Madhya Pradesh, India

Şcoala de Valori Lead Trainer January 2018 - March 2018 (3 months) Romania

- 1. Designs an educational session based on specific topics and learning objectives for GROW participants.
- 2. Delivers 10 different educational sessions in English to the Youth of Romania.
- 3. Organizes events together with the Young students.

TED Conferences Speaker April 2018 - 2018 (less than a year) United States

United Nations Speaker May 2015 - June 2015 (2 months) Austria

Jaguar Land Rover Social Media Marketing Consultant August 2014 - April 2015 (9 months) Indore Area, India

AIESEC

Team Member August 2013 - February 2014 (7 months)

Education

Prestige Institute of Management and Research
Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), Business Administration and
Management, General · (2013 - 2016)

National Public School High School, Business/Commerce, General · (2000 - 2013)